No Half Measures: Creating the Final Season of Breaking Bad is a
documentary film directed by Stuart Richardson.
A documentary about the making of season five of the
acclaimed AMC series Breaking Bad.
Self, played by Bryan Cranston.
Self, played by Aaron Paul.
Self, played by Anna Gunn.
Self, played by Dean Norris.
Self, played by Betsy Brandt.
Self, played by RJ Mitte.
Breaking Bad is an American neo-Western crime drama television
series created and produced by Vince Gilligan for AMC.
Set and filmed in Albuquerque, New Mexico, the series follows Walter White (Bryan Cranston), an over-qualified,
dispirited high-school chemistry teacher struggling with a recent diagnosis of stage-three lung cancer.
White turns to a life of crime and partners with a former student, Jesse Pinkman (Aaron Paul), to produce and distribute
methamphetamine to secure his family's financial future before he dies, while navigating the dangers of the criminal underworld.
The series also stars Anna Gunn, Dean Norris, RJ Mitte, Betsy Brandt,
Giancarlo Esposito, Jonathan Banks, and Bob Odenkirk.
Breaking Bad premiered on AMC on January 20, 2008, and concluded on
September 29, 2013, after five seasons and 62 episodes.
Breaking Bad's first season received generally positive reviews, while the subsequent seasons (especially the fifth and final season) received
universal critical acclaim, with praise for the performances, direction, cinematography, writing, story, and character development.
The show had fair viewership in its first three seasons, but the fourth and fifth seasons saw a moderate rise
in viewership when it was made available on Netflix just before the fourth season premiere.
Viewership increased exponentially upon the premiere of the
second half of the fifth season in 2013.
By the time that the series finale aired, it was among the
most-watched cable shows on American television.
Since its conclusion, the show has been lauded by critics as one
of the greatest television series of all time.
It has also developed a cult following and has received numerous awards, including 16 Primetime Emmy Awards, 8 Satellite Awards, 2 Golden Globe
Awards, 2 Peabody Awards, 2 Critics' Choice Awards, 4 Television Critics Association Awards and 1 British Academy Television Award.
Cranston won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series four times, Paul won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding
Supporting Actor in a Drama Series three times, and Gunn won the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series twice.
In 2013, Breaking Bad entered the Guinness World Records as the
most critically acclaimed TV show of all time.
In 2023, Breaking Bad was ranked as the best TV series in the last 25
years by critics in a poll conveyed by Rotten Tomatoes.
The series gave rise to the larger Breaking Bad franchise.
Better Call Saul, a prequel series featuring Odenkirk, Banks, and Esposito reprising their Breaking Bad roles, as well as many
others in guest and recurring appearances, debuted on AMC on February 8, 2015, and concluded on August 15, 2022.
El Camino: A Breaking Bad Movie, a sequel film starring Paul, was
released on Netflix and in theaters on October 11, 2019.